believeth if this is the last time I
talked to you I want you to know
I did your mom
yeah
I don't want a part of Steward in me
look at him what if I start to suck I'm
scared hey
um you know what I'm beginning to have
second thoughts about this hope okay
count backwards from ten hey hey I'm
hungry
and now you count backwards from ten ten
um eight or something uh five I don't
know W
um I am the great cornhole
is this Tyler the Creator
uh yeah
I mean he's calling everything but a man
he kind of needs a better name you know
if I was gonna be one of these guys I'd
be like Butthead the scorer
Abby Beavis the mutilator
she'd be Beavis the monkey spanker
I think it's another nice ring to it
his choice you know but
[Music]
if I was stranded on a Lifeboat with
that girl
I'd be like hey baby you ever do it on a
boat with three dudes and raincoats and
masturbating
yeah make that four yeah
damn it baby you're messing up my flow
again